

# Christopher Taylor Gonzalez Rivera

FULL STACK DEVELOPER JAVASCRIPT

With a Master's degree in Computer Science and a background in Electronics Engineering, I have over five years of experience as a Full Stack Developer, specializing in MERN technologies (MongoDB, Express JS, React, NodeJS). My expertise lies in developing applications for Industry 4.0 and IoT, enabling real-time monitoring of variables for efficient decision-making.

# taylorgr@outlook.com

+52 33 3172 8350

https://taylorgr93.com

Zapopan, Jalisco, Mexico.

#### ACADEMIC TRAINING

- Master's degree in Computer Science at Universidad Autonoma de Guadalajara, 2020 - 2022
- Electronic engineering at Centro de Enseñanza Tecnica Industrial (CETI), 2012 - 2016

#### OTHERS SKILLS

- JavaScript ES6, TypeScript
- Yarn, NPM Axios, Fetch, JWT, ApiGateway, Git
- React Hooks, Redux, Zustand, JEST, Context API, Webpack
- Material UI, Tailwind CSS
- Scrum, JIRA, Monday
- HTML, CSS, C#, Python, C++
- SQL Server, MySQL, PostgreSQL
- RESTful APIs, JSON, XML

#### SOFT SKILLS

- Teamwork, Communication, Work ethic
- · Self-motivation ,Compromise, Creativity
- Problem solving, Continuos lerning

## WORK EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER GRUPO ABSA, May 2019 - today

Creating Industry 4.0 and IoT Applications for Effective Decision-Making Our team specializes in developing applications that allow end-users to monitor variables in real-time and make informed decisions based on the results.

- Expertise in full-stack development, including MongoDB,
- Express JS, React JS, Node JS, and JEST.
- Cloud computing proficiency with AWS, including EC2, S3, and Lambda.
  - Container handling with Docker and Docker Compose.
- In-depth knowledge of the Linux command line, task and script running, system administration, and configuration.
- Experience developing REST Full API services for the seamless integration of GPS location services and Motorola RF communication services.

### SOFTWARE TEST ENGINEER

JABIL CIRCUIT MEXICO, November 2018 - April 2019

- Development of web applications for product validation (ASP.Net Core Framework, HTML, JavaScript, CSS).
- Support applications for product validation (PHP, phpMyAdmin).
- Development of applications for process automation (.NET).

# SUPPORT ENGINEER

POUNCE CONSULTING, August 2016 - November 2018

- Creation of .NET applications for electronic meter validation.
- Development of user-friendly graphical interfaces to automate production lines and streamline validation processes.
- Proficient in database design and management for SQL server and MySQL systems.
- Experience with version control systems including hg mercurial, svn and git.
- Dedicated customer support throughout the project.
- Knowledgeable in electronic manufacturing production lines.